Humanities Council 2018.027
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Humanities Council
2013-2017
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
DC Community Humanities Council
2018.027
2 Linear feet
Humanities; Organizational Records
- Series 1: Grant Files
  - 13-WWG-10 University of District of Columbia, 2013-2017 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 14-HAT Festival-01 Double Nickels Theatre Company, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 14-HAT Festival -02 Eagles Nest Youth Association, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 14-HAT Festival-03 Split This Rock, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 14-HAT Festival-04 The National Hand Dance Asociation, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 14-HAT Festival-05 Will Rap 4 Food Inc, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 14-Shimel Lode Grant-01 Audra Polk, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 14-Shimel Lode Grant-02 Charles T. Downey, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 14-Shimel Lode Grant-03 Sarah Elwell, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 14-Shimel Lode Grant-04 Double Nickels Theatre Company, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 14-Shimel Lode Grant-05 One Common Unity, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 14-Remembrance-01 AIA Legacy dba AIA Foundation, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 14-Remembrance-02 Arts for Our Children, Inc., 2014 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 14-Remembrance-03 DC Independent Film Festival, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 14-Remembrance-04 Smithsonian Institution, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 14-Remembrance-05 Women in Film & Video, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 14-SM/PL-01 Bowie State University, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 14-SM/PL-02 Day Eight, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 14-SM/PL-03 Funk Parade, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 14-SM/PL-04 Stone Soup Films, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 14-SOTC-01 Split This Rock, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 14-SOTC-02 Mentors of Minorities in Education, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 14-SOTC-03 Global Kids, Inc, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 14-WWG-01 1882 Project Foundation, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 14-WWG-02 Center for Inspired Teaching, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 14-WWG-03 Dance Institute of Washington, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 14-WWG-04 Endangered Species Coalition, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 14-WWG-06 Teaching for Change, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 14-WWG-05 Positive Productions, Inc., 2014 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 14-WWG-07 The L'Enfant Trust, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 14-WWG-08 Washington DC Jewish Community Center, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 14-WWG-09 Washington Performing Arts, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 14-WWG-10 Will Rap 4 Food Inc., 2014 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 14-01-01 All Souls Housing Corp, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 14-01-02 Chowan Discovery Group, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 14-01-03 Community Resources Incorporated, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 14-01-04 DC Youth Orchestra Program, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 14-01-05 Diversity Thearte Co., 2014 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 14-01-06 Docs in Progress, 2014-2018 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 14-01-07 Festivals DC, Ltd, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 14-01-08 From Block2Block, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 14-01-09 I SAW! DC, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 14-01-10 PEN/Faulkner Foundation, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 14-01-11 Washington Architectural Foundation, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 14-DCCHP-01 Anacostia Community Outreach Center, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 14-DCCHP-02 Black Student Fund, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 14-DCCHP-03 DC African American Legacy Foundation, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 14-DCCHP-04 DC Preservation League, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 14-DCCHP-05 Ecohermanas, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 14-DCCHP-06 Empower DC, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 14-DCCHP-07 Jewish Historical Society of Greater Washington, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 14-DCCHP-08 KhushDC, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 14-DCCHP-09 Local Initiatives Support Corporation, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 14-DCCHP-10 Parklands Community Center, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 14-DCCHP-11 Rehoboth Baptist Church Historical Committee, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 14-DCCHP-12 San ctuary Theatre, Inc, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 14-DCCHP-13 The Potter's House, 2014-2017 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 14-DCCHP-14 United Planning Organization, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 14-DCCHP-15 Urban Rangers Youth Group/Centronia, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 14-DCCHP-16 Wilson HS PTSO, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 27)